esnipe.com 2003-06-21

# eSnipe Privacy Statement

|  | 

   Log In

   Join eSnipe

**What are Bid Groups?**   
Bid Groups allow you to combine multiple bids into one group and **automatically cancel the remaining bids after the first one wins**. Click here for how to use Bid Groups.    
  
**eSnipe 3.0 information page**   
**Questions or problems?** Remember to click the eSnipe 3.0 New Site Information banner at the top of the page for information and directions to contact support.  

|  |  |  (Last updated 23:15 PDT May 28 2001)

**What information do we collect?**  
When you join esnipe, we ask for some information that will identify you to us as a user. This information includes your name, email address, eBay username and eBay password. We require your eBay username and password in order to place bids on your behalf. Without these, esnipe could not place a bid on eBay for you. We may also ask you to supply a handful of demographic statistics. This is for aggregate purposes only. It is not stored with your other information, and can not ever be associated with you or your account - even by esnipe.

We also collect statistical data about the bids being placed by the esnipe servers. This information is also aggregrate, and is not associated with you or your account. 

**What do you do with this information?**  
eSnipe **never** supplies your personal information to any third party for advertising or promotional purposes. If you owe money to eSnipe and we're unable to collect it, we may need to give your contact information to a third party for collection purposes. We will occasionally use your email address to send you information regarding esnipe and the services we provide. Your eBay username and password are stored in our database, and can only be changed by you once you have logged into the system. Your username and password are transmitted to eBay when esnipe places a bid on your behalf.

The information we collect about bids is summarized, and we provide basic information to our advertisers on the general product categories our members are interested in. **Is my information secure?**  
Your personal information is protected by your password. Never share this password with anyone. esnipe will never contact you unsolicited to ask for your password. We have taken steps to ensure our databases are secure, and are confident in our ability to keep your information safe. However, please note that the bid pages on eBay are not encrypted, and therefore when esnipe, or yourself for that matter, places a bid - your username and password are sent over the Internet without encryption. Because of this, esnipe can not guarantee 100% protection of your password when a bid is being placed. **What about cookies?**  
eSnipe stores a cookie on your computer to track you while you are on the site. The information in this cookie is a string of characters that is meaningless to everyone and everything except our server. No personal information or bid information is stored in the cookie. The information in the cookie can not be used by third parties to gain access to your account information. **Still have questions?**  
We realize everyone has a different view on privacy. We take your privacy very seriously. If you still have concerns, or are unclear about any aspect of our privacy policy, please contact us, and we will be happy to discuss the matter with you.   
---|---|---|---|---
